Guide to the Eastern Parkway Coalition records 2007.016
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 2: Plans and maps, 1973-1988; 21416; 1.5 Linear Feet in six rolled document cases, one oversize flat box, and one loose rolled item
  The series contains plans and maps for the reconstruction and redevelopment of Eastern Parkway and other streets in the Prospect Heights and Crown Heights neighborhoods of Brooklyn, dating from 1973 to 1988. The series also includes district maps and plans for playground reconstruction. There are eleven sets of plans and maps in total, along with two folders of related documents. The plans and maps were produced by the City of New York.
  - New York Housing and Development Administration - Crown Heights Community Planning Districts No. 8 and 9 map, 1973; 21429 (Object 16, Folder -)
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway plans, 1983; 21424 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Reconstruction of the Playground and Comfort Station at Underhill Avenue and Prospect Place, Brooklyn, 1984; 21419 (Box 10)
    Conditions Governing Access
    These rolled architectural plans are too fragile to be handled by researchers.
  - Eastern Parkway Maintenance of Traffic general plan, 1986; 21423 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway from Ralph Avenue and Pitkin Avenue plans, 1986; 21428 (Box 15, Folder -)
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway plans (1 of 2), 1986; 21417 (Oversize OS-30)
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway plans (2 of 2), 1986; 21418 (Box 10)
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway plans, 1986; 21427 (Folder 1)
    Plans for streelights, ornamentation, etc.
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway plans (1 of 2), 1986-1988; 21425 (Oversize OS-30)
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway plans (2 of 2), 1986-1988; 21426 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Bergen Street and Dean Street - Prospect Heights/Crown Heights maps, circa 1980s; 21420 (Box 10)
  - Reconstruction of Vanderbilt Avenue intersection at Atlantic Avenue, from Pacific Street to approximately 150 feet north of north building line, circa 1980s; 21421 (Box 11)
  - Reconstruction of Dean Street, from Flatbush Avenue to Rochester Avenue, and Bergen Street, from Flatbush Avenue to Albany Avenue, plans, circa 1980s; 21422 (Box 11)